Viewers all over the world, we have received the Word of God.
What a wonderful grace.
What a God we serve.
I can see God's healing, God's deliverance touching you.
I can see God's deliverance touching you.
One thing we must know -
God will not move us to pray for something that is not sanctioned by the Scripture.
Your heart must act upon the Word.
Your heart must act upon the Word because God will not move me
to pray for something that is not sanctioned by the Scripture.
Receive a hearing heart!
A hearing heart is an obedient heart.
Receive, in the name of Jesus!
I command that deliverance on you, in the name of Jesus!
Be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
I command all unclean spirits operating in your life to leave, in the name of Jesus!
Leave my people!
Spirit of failure,
spirit of setback,
spirit of nightmare,
spirit of affliction - leave my people!
Whatever chain satan might have used,
whatever medium satan might have used to connect you to himself -
be broken, in the name of Jesus!
I can hear chains falling -
chain of affliction,
chain of setback,
chain of failure,
chain of disease.
In the name of Jesus Christ, receive a new direction!
Receive a new focus!
Receive a new direction!
Receive a new focus, in Jesus' name!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I can hear breakthrough!
Breakthrough!
In your business - breakthrough!
In your career - breakthrough!
In your marriage - breakthrough!
In your health - breakthrough!
In Jesus' name!
Rejoice!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
TT: Anonymous
RV: Mel Flowers 14/12/2018